(Sheldon:)Oh, I don't mind, I'm very good
at complaining.
(Sheldon:)If it were an Olympic sport,
I'd complain about
(Sheldon:)what a stupid sport it is
and then I'd take home the gold.
(Amy:)Good stuff.
(Amy:)So, uh, what about dinner?
(Sheldon:)Is it me
(Sheldon:)or are you purposely
changing the subject?
(Howard(singing):)No.
(Amy:)And on the subject of subjects,
(Amy:)is your use of the word
"subject" the same or different
(Amy:)as when we speak about
the subject of a king?
(Sheldon:)I have a feeling
you're still doing it.
(Sheldon:)But I find that topic
irresistible, so,
(Sheldon:)now, in ancient Mesopotamia,
(Sheldon:)the king referred to the people
as his property.
(Howard:)I'm serious,
(Howard:)JPL's actually
developing a robot arm
(Howard:)that could grab an asteroid
before it hits us.
(Leonard:)So their plan for saving
the Earth from Armageddon
(Leonard:)is hoping a bunch of
scientists can catch a ball?
(Raj:)If we're all gonna die,
why am I eating so much kale?